{
    "subject": "resource/Kalash,_Ardabil",
    "predicate": "property/pushpinMap",
    "object": "Iran",
    "human_readable": "The location of Kalash, Ardabil on a map is Iran.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8190833926200867,
            "question": "Where is Kalash located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.748351514339447,
            "question": "Can you describe the geographical location of Kalash?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6221347451210022,
            "question": "In which province is Kalash situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5307251214981079,
            "question": "What are some notable landmarks or features near Kalash?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5285392999649048,
            "question": "Is Kalash a city or a region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48359861969947815,
            "question": "What country is Kalash in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3297524154186249,
            "question": "Are there any historical events associated with Kalash?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26001423597335815,
            "question": "Is there anything unique about Kalash's climate or terrain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25856825709342957,
            "question": "What is the population of Kalash?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15233619511127472,
            "question": "Does Kalash have a significant cultural heritage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The location of Kalash, Ardabil on a map is Iran.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6507_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Kalash?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6507_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything unique about Kalash's climate or terrain?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6507_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical events associated with Kalash?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6507_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6507_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6507_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6507_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6507_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6507_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6507_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6507_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6507_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6507_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6507_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that the geographical location of Kalash is East Azarbayejan, Iran. Therefore, the statement that the location of Kalash on a map is in Iran is correct according to the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}